Now then, what should I make tonight?
I know Mana said she wanted to eat curry.
What on Earth?
What happened?
Was that actually a spatial quake?
All citizens, please remain indoors
until instructed otherwise!
Also, airwaves are being overloaded,
so please do your part
by refraining from using phones
Big Brother! I'm so glad to see you... safe?
and other communication devices
as much as possible!
We ask that you please remain calm!
Big Brother?
Mana?! Well, you see, this is—
Don't worry! I'm on your side, Big Brother!
Let's take our time to repent
for the sins you've committed!
Nothing you're assuming is okay!
I understand the situation.
But still!
That didn't mean you had to
bring her to our place!
What else could I do?
The city's in a panic,
and she won't say anything to me,
so I had no idea what I should do.
Achoo!
For starters, let's have her wear my clothes!
I'll go get some right now, so—
Huh?
Danger Do Not Cross
Fafner
in the Azure
History and Economics
I see.
I mostly have the language system down now.
What's the matter?
What do you mean? You just—
"Ah" and "Unh" were all
you could say yesterday,
and now you're suddenly speaking fluently,
so of course we'd be surprised.
You're using more proper Japanese than Mana.
Hmm?!
Big Brother, I think you might be saying
only "ah" and "unh" for a while.
Wait! Calm down!
I love how unique you are!
So long as you understand.
By the way, I'd like to ask,
but who exactly are you?
You're clearly not a normal person.
Does yesterday's spatial quake
have any connection to you?
I'm sorry, I don't know.
It doesn't seem like she's lying.
Then could you tell us
what you do know at least?
Um, I'd like to know more about you.
What I remember...
is a vast horizon following some kind of
explosion like the one from yesterday.
There were three people there.
Two young men and one little girl.
Three people?
Following an explosion like yesterday's?
You were there at
the Great Eurasian Spatial Quake?
A-Are you okay?
I'm fine. I just felt a little pain.
I see. Please don't push yourself.
Thank you.
Ah!
So, Big Brother, what are you
planning to do with this woman?
What will I do?
The police should—
N-No, wait!
Both hospitals and the police
are busy after yesterday.
If we just tossed her into their care
without warning, then...
I know.
I guess we'll just wait and see
for now while she stays with us?
It doesn't seem like she's a bad person.
You're going to let me stay here?
Yes.
Since our father and mother
aren't here right now.
Uh...
That reminds me, we haven't
introduced ourselves, have we?
Neither of us have shared our names.
Names?
That's right. I'm Shinji Takamiya,
and this is my little sister,
Mana Takamiya.
Shinji and Mana Takamiya...
So, what's your name?
You do have a name, right?
My name?
Uh, you don't need to force
yourself to remember.
Your memories might naturally
come back on their own in time.
But it's inconvenient
if she doesn't have a name.
We need something to call her.
In that case, well...
May
I know, Mio!
Mio?
Mio, written with zero and
the water radical to make waterway.
Oh, that's not bad.
By the way, how did you come up with that?
Well, yesterday was May 30th, right?
So 3-0 can be read as Mio.
Mio.
Still, we have public
appearances to worry about,
so for a while we'll say
you're a family member.
Meaning your full name will be Mio Takamiya!
Mio Takamiya?
Huh?
That's strange.
I'm happy, so why am I...?
This is...
Hey, Ike.
Do you really think she's in this town?
She might have run away
somewhere else already.
I just hope she's safe at least.
All right!
I finally nabbed it.
Here you go, Mio.
Huh?
You're giving it to me?
That's why I nabbed it.
Or did you not want it?
You kept looking at it during our walk,
so I assumed you love stuff like this.
Love...
To view something favorably...
To be drawn to something
with strong interest...
That's it!
Yeah, I'm sure this is love!
I love you!
Uh, Mio.
If you'd like, would you go on a
d-date with me?!
I should practice a bit more.
G-Good morning, Mio.
Nice weather we're having, huh?
Want to go out for a bit?
No, that's not right.
We go shopping together all the time anyway.
I want it to be more.
A real date.
I want Mio to think of it as a date, too.
Uh, ahem, ahem.
Mio, let's go on a date.
Sure!
M-Mio?!
Yeah? What's the matter, Shin?
H-How long have you been there?
Since you said, "No, that's not right."
So, Shin, when are we going?
Huh? G-Going on what?
On our date.
A date?!
Yeah.
Y-You're going on a date?!
My shy, unsociable big brother
asked you out on a date?!
Yeah.
Though thinking about it,
a date is just a man and woman
meeting up together, right?
I'm with Shin every day,
so I'm not really sure what it means to
go out together in a more formal sense.
Well, in short it means big brother
wants to grow even closer to you, Mio!
You could say he's trying to
show you his affection.
Mio?
I see!
Shin feels affection toward me...
That makes me happy.
Jeez!
All right!
In that case, let's get you prepared!
I heard what's going on!
I'm Haruko Homura, Mana's BFF!
Leave this to me!
BFF?
Yeah, it's not in the dictionary,
so don't worry about the word.
Haruko knows a lot about fashion,
so I called her in to help.
I know you told me before,
but she really is a pretty woman.
Who's the lucky boy who's
getting to date such a beauty?
Well, my big brother.
Huh?!
For real?! Way to go!
All right, I've got it!
This is going to be well worth it
in all kinds of ways!
First, I need to equip my focus enhancing item!
Now which should we go with?
U-Um, I'm counting on you.
Shin...
What's the matter? You had a scary look...
S-Sorry.
Did I look that scary?
You did.
You looked like you were
going off to war or something.
War, huh?
Sorry, I was spacing out.
It's just... y-you're way too cute!
W-Well, then...
Shall we go?
Yeah!
Shall we start our date?
The ocean...
You said you wanted to see it
someday, right?
I'm so happy!
Thank you, Shin!
Yeah, I'm glad that you're enjoying it.
Mio!
Wow!
The hem of your skirt is—
Shin!
Mio!
H-Hey, Mio!
M-Mio?!
Achoo!
What are we doing for dinner tonight?
I haven't decided yet.
Is there anything you'd like to eat, Mio?
I'm happy with any food you make, Shin.
Mio?
This way!
Mio! What's gotten into you?!
I'll explain later!
Hurry!
Who are you people?!
Shin, grab on to me!
Huh?!
Shin!
I'm all right. We need to hurry!
Show me your hand.
Huh?
Hey!
Shh!
Who on earth were those guys?
They're probably after me.
Huh?!
I've started to remember.
When I first woke up that man
from before was in front of me.
Then he tried to capture me.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault you've gotten wrapped up in this.
Run.
I'll handle the rest.
No way!
I was ready to face some trouble
from the moment I took in a girl
with mysterious powers.
We're family now.
Anyway, let's slip out to where
there are lots of people.
Then we'll go to the police.
Don't underestimate the rule of law!
Get back!
Mio!
Don't worry, I won't kill him!
Hey now, are you serious?
Why would you to come to me of all places?
Huh?!
Hmm, so is Mio that woman's name?
Yeah, I gave it to her.
I see. It's a good name.
Hey, are you happy right now?
At the very least, I don't enjoy being
chased around by people hostile to me!
No, I'm not referring to that.
I was talking about being
with that guy beside you.
I see.
Then scram.
What's the meaning of this?
There's nothing else to it.
Hurry up and go already.
Boy... Take care of that girl, Mio.
It's been a long time, Spirit.
I've missed you.
It's my first time meeting that boy there.
Thank you for taking care of our Spirit.
I truly am grateful.
Don't give me that!
We have your little sister in custody.
Now, why don't we return
both women to where they belong?
Why you!
Just try doing anything to Mana!
I'll never forgive you if you do!
Oh? Her name is Mana, then?
That's quite the joke.
I can understand why our Spirit
would wind up there.
Promise me.
If I go with you, then you'll return Mana.
Yes, of course we will.
Mio?!
It's okay.
I was never supposed to exist here anyway.
Even spending a short time
with you made me happy.
Screw that!
Shin! What are you—?!
Idiot!
Do you really think he'll keep his promise?!
What guarantee do we have that he won't
just kill me and Mana once we has you, Mio?!
So as long as you're with us,
they can't lay a hand on Mana!
So it would be way better to stay
with me and shore up our position!
Shin?
Good grief.
I wasn't actually lying, you know.
Shin!
Mi...
o...
Right.
I can just recreate him.
I'll never let go of you again.
I won't make any more mistakes.
So...
wait for me,
Shin.
Episode 4
The Spirit's Resurrection
Episode 5 "Mother Mio"
Mio Takamiya,
the mother of all Spirits.
As the battle rages on,
some confront their most beloved
and others confront their hated enemies.
Next episode is Episode 5: "Mother Mio."
The blossoms of death bloom in the sky.